各位自由媒体的清廉护民官 (古罗马官职)
So, incorruptible tribunes of the free press,
请享用这些芬兰式早餐
please enjoy this Finnish breakfast.
正如你们所知 副总统最近与芬兰签署了
As you know, the vice president recently signed
一项十分具有历史意义的软件合作协议
an historic software agreement with Finland.
她的欧洲访问是否被那首歌的阴影笼罩?
Wasn't her trip to Europe overshadowed by the song?
你知道的 就是那首她嘲笑欧洲人的歌
You know, the one where she mocked Europeans?
她没有嘲笑欧洲人
She wasn't mocking Europeans.
我会说那首歌很搞笑 搞笑?
- I would say the song was jesty. - Jesty?
但更重要的是 现在副总统
But more importantly, right now the vice president
正与国会多数党领袖Mary King会晤
is meeting with the House Majority Leader Mary King.
她们正在协商一项
And they are brokering a debt reduction deal
能避免政府停工的债务削减
that's going to avert a government shutdown.
Selina Meyer将成为美国史上
Selina Meyer's becoming one of the most
最有效率的副总统之一
effective American vice presidents in history.
在解救乌兹别克斯坦人质事件中她起了关键性的作用
She was crucial in the freeing of the Uzbekistan hostages.
对吗? 是的
Correct? - Yes.
那个软件
The software--
她知道其中一个人质是间谍
Did she know that one of the hostages was a spy
而使得其他三个学生的生命受到了威胁吗?
endangering the other three students?
Um...
或许当时不是很清楚
possibly not quite at the time.
那么她那些说她自己在这次军事解救行动中
So all this stuff she's been saying about
扮演了重要角色的话都是谎言咯
being a crucial part of the military rescue is a lie.
好吧 慢一点 Leon 你的血糖太低了吗?
Okay, slow down, Leon. Is your blood sugar off?
不如来点点心或者鲱鱼 怎么样?
Have a pastry or some herring, okay?
请回答问题 我不知道她知道什么
- Answer the question. - I don't know what she knew
或者她是何时知道的 Leon Mike Mike
- or when she knew it, Leon. - Mike, Mike.
要么她知道那个学生是个间谍
Either she knew that the student was a spy
然后在否认这件事的时候撒了谎
and lied when she denied it,
要么她不知道他是间谍
or she didn't know that he was a spy,
但是谎称自己知道这次军事解救行动的细节
but lied about knowing the details of the military rescue.
这不是又一次说谎者Meyer 事件
This isn't Meyer the Liar again.
哦 现在是了
Well, it is now.
这不是个容易事儿 Selina
This isn't going to be a cakewalk, Selina.
哦 这是艰难的协议谈判
- Oh. - This one's the hard bargaining.
你不担心吗 我知道如何讨价还价
Don't you worry. I know how to haggle.
当然
You betcha.
你儿子还好吗 他们很不错
- How are your boys? - They're great.
Catherine呢 她21了
- How's Catherine? - She's 21.
棒极了 是的 今晚我们会给她举办个派对
- That's great. - Yeah, we're having her party tonight.
所以我现在很兴奋 今晚?
- So I'm excited about that. - Tonight?
是的 你知道 对孩子们你所有的希望就是
Yeah. You know, all you ever want for these kids
他们快乐健康 没错
is to be happy And healthy. - Right. You bet.
那是肯定的 而且远离中东政治
And stay out of Middle East politics.
所以以上三点中有两个不那么糟糕
So two out of three ain't bad.
我很惊讶你居然能拿那个开玩笑
I'm amazed you can laugh about that.
是的 那就是我做的事 我在自嘲
Yes, that's what I do. I'm laughing about it.
她的那个男朋友...
She has that boyfriend.
你觉得他么会结婚吗? 我们是不是该继续…
- You think that's going to actually lead to a marriage? - Should we get going...
手边的事情? 没错 没错
- with this business at hand? - Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
我很好奇里面进行得怎么样了
I wonder how it's going in there.
这就像等待活组织检查的结果
It's like waiting for a biopsy result.
Mary是个狠角色
Mary's a player.
她曾经假装昏倒而在和Brian Earl的谈判中占了上风
She did own Brian Earl in negotiations by pretending to faint.
那么今晚Catherine的生日派对后 要不要一起去吃点什么?
So after Catherine's birthday party tonight, you want to grab a bite?
说说赫尔辛基 策划一下?
Talk about Helsinki, strategize a little bit?
今晚我有约了 是哦
I have a date for tonight. -  Yeah.
哦?
Yeah?
是谁? Ed
Who is it? - Ed.
哦 Ed是做什么的
Ooh, and what does Ed do?
Ed Webster是党内筹款人
Ed Webster is a fund-raiser for the party
他过去五年为Selina工作
and he's worked for Selina for the past five years.
Sue 插话回答问题
Sue. - Cracked under the questioning.
他也是Selina的人?
He's one of Selina's guys?
你发过誓只会和特区外的人约会
You swore you were only gonna date outside DC.
他不在特区 他在波士顿工作
He's not in DC. He works in Boston.
好吧 我妈也不住在罗马 但她仍然是个他妈的天主教徒
Well, my mom doesn't live in Rome, but she's still a fucking Catholic.
你被刺激了 Danny? 闭上你的臭嘴 Gary
- Are you getting worked up, Danny? - Shut the fuck up, Gary.
我正开心你为我高兴 Dan
I'm so happy you're happy for me, Dan.
哦 你想要什么 他大爷的蛋糕?
Oh, what do you want, a fucking cake?
瞧 我可以很开心 看见了吗?
Look, I can be happy. See?
这下好了吧
There you go.
这儿唯一的真正削减是失业保险
The only real cut here is unemployment insurance.
Mary 你知道总统不会削减
Mary, POTUS is not gonna make any cuts
任何失业保险的
to unemployment insurance and you know that.
需要我向你解释讨价还价是如何运作的吗
Do I need to explain to you how haggling works?
那全国卫生研究所削减10% 如何?
How about a 10% cut to NIH, okay?
我要20% 那个数字我没法做到
- I need 20. - I can't do those numbers.
那行不通
That's not gonna work.
上帝保佑你 谢谢
- God bless you. - Thank you.
那么唯一的简单解决方案就是失业保险
Then the only obvious solution is unemployment insurance.
不 我告诉过你了 我做不到
No, I told you. I can't do that.
你在干嘛?
What are you doing?
什么
What?
你在拖延时间吗
You stalling for time?
让我给你拿些纸巾 可以吗?
Let me get you a Kleenex, yeah?
我想这结束了 喷嚏总是不超过三个
I think it's over. Sneezes always come in threes.
你有注意过那个吗? 真的 是那样吗?
have You ever noticed that? - Really? is that so?
哦 好吧 第四个了
Oh, well, that was a fourth.
那么或许我该告诉你怎么数数(做账) 对吗？
So maybe I need to tell you about how counting works, right?
好了 好的
- All right. - Okay.
我们可以提高... 什么?
We Can raise fees... - the What?
印第安那卫生局的费用 唔? 你要昏倒了吗?
- ...on Indian Health Services. - Hmm? You gonna faint?
我不... 哦 真好笑
I'm not-- oh, very funny.
你要喝点水吗? 是的
Do You want water? - Yes.
我去给你拿些水
I'll get you some water.
我会给你拿些水 好的
- I'm gonna get you water. - Okay.
怎么样了 女士? 喔 你对她十分强硬 嗯?
- How's it going, ma'am? - Wow, you're really hardballing her, huh?
不 她正假装把她的内脏咳出来
No, she's pretending to cough herself inside out.
能请你给她拿些水吗?
Could you get her some water, please?
我不知道什么...
I don't know what--
哦!哦 天啊!Mary 你还好吗
Ooh! Oh, my God! Mary, are you all right?
我想我这是过敏反应
I think I'm having an allergic reaction.
你对什么过敏? 这里有猫毛吗
What are You allergic to? - is there cat hair?
我有养猫 哦 Gary有猫
- I have cats. - Oh, Gary has cats.
等等 Gary Gary Gary 我们需要水
Wait, Gary, Gary, Gary. We need the water.
哦 给你 是这个马海毛?
Yeah, there you go. Is it this mohair?
可能是这个马海毛 你觉得呢
it Might be the mohair. - Do You think?
不 她在这呆过 坚果?是这些坚果吗?
- No, she's been here-- - The nuts? Is it the nuts?
你吃了坚果吗?没有? 不是
did You eat nuts? No? - Mm-mmm.
是不是这些花? 什么?
is it the flowers? - What?
我为Catherine生日准备的
The ones I got for Catherine's birthday.
哦 基督啊!这些该死的东西!
Oh, Christ! Those fuckers!
就是那个 我去 好吧 都好了 抱歉
- That's it. - Shit, okay. All right, sorry.
哦 上帝啊 Gary 快把房里的花都采走 (开苞)
- Oh, God. - Gary, deflower the room.
我打赌你根本没想过能听见这种话
There's a sentence I bet you thought you'd never hear.
我没法支持另外四个小时
I'm not good for another four hours.
Selina 我们今晚再说
Selina, we've got to take this up tonight.
Mary 我要给女儿过21岁生日
Mary, I've got my daughter's 21st birthday.
别去 我不可能不去她...
- Don't go. - I can't not go to her--
你会错过你儿子民事结合的庆典吗? (一般为同性伴侣采用)
Would you miss your son's Civil Union ceremony?
我是没去 哦
I did. - Oh.
好吧 那么 你得来Catherine的派对
Well, then, you have to come to Catherine's.
我们会在今晚完成它 是的 我们会的 今晚
- We've got to finish this tonight. - Yes, we do, tonight.
来吧 你可以带一个伴
Come. You can bring a plus one.
在他妈的氧气罐上贴上外套和领带
Stick a coat and tie on a fucking oxygen tank.
Mike Leon West打到我这里两次
Mike, Leon West called my line twice.
你又把手机丢了?
Did you lose your phone again?
不 Leon对整个间谍事件有点点怀疑
No, Leon's a little skeptical about the whole spy thing
而有蠢货又再次提起了说谎者Meyer
and some dumbass is resurrecting Meyer the Liar.
呃 就因为我的姓和说谎者押韵
Ugh, just because my last name rhymes with liar.
多亏我不是Selina Mapist (音近强奸犯)
How lucky am I that I'm not Selina Mapist
或者Selina Medophile (音近恋童癖者)
or Selina Medophile?
我刚看到Mary King了 她看起来就像被鲸鱼呕吐出来了一样
I just saw Mary King. Looked like she's been thrown up by a whale.
是的 她被过敏症袭击了
Yeah, she had an allergy attack.
那么你们完成协议了?告诉我你完成了
So did you do the deal? Tell me you did the deal.
今天晚上我会完成它 她会去Catherine的生日派对
I'm gonna finish it tonight. She's coming to Catherine's birthday party.
天啊 你知道 如果我们没有在午夜前搞定
Jesus. You know, if we don't get this done by midnight,
我们就会变成丑姐姐们然后被狼吃掉了 (灰姑娘及小红帽混搭)
we're all gonna turn into ugly sisters and get eaten by wolves
不管那个故事到底是什么破结尾
or whatever the fuck happens at the end of that story.
音爆小子前来报到 女士
Sonic boom in the room. Ma'am.
不 哦 好吧
- No. - Oh, okay.
好吧 总统要我来这
Well, POTUS wanted me to come down here
打探一下债务谈判的内部消息
and peep the skinny on the debt negotiations.
好吧 这个是火灾隐患 那么让我们就...
Okay, that's a fire hazard, so let's just...
Gary 我是被总统派下来的...
Gary, I have been sent here from the president.
好吧 那个 总统已经承受了很多
Okay, so the president's already going through a lot of pressure
那个人质谎言破事的压力了
about this hostage lying bullshit.
他饱受压力? 没错
- He's under pressure? - Yes.
我才饱受压力 好吧 你是有选择的
- I'm under pressure. - Well, you do have a choice.
你可以说人质解救事件中你没有被告知所有事情
You could say you were out of the loop for the hostage rescue,
这可以让你看起来无能 或者你可以选择说你确实知道
which would make you look clueless, or you could say you were in the loop,
而那会让你被认作不正直
which would make you look devious.
随便哪个 只要他妈的把它糊弄过去就行
Either way, just blur the fuck out of it.
Uh-huh.
哦 去他的 女士
- Oh, fuck. - Ma'am.
有任何事要我...
Anything that I should--
Amy Ed Webster来见你了
Amy, Ed Webster is here to see you.
我想他很紧张 他的声音听起来很僵硬
I think he's nervous. His voice sounded clammy.
哦 好吧 那不错 那不错
Oh, okay. That's good. That's good.
看你那慌张的样子
Look at you all flustered.
你很快就能滚床单了挺好的
It's good that you'll have sex soon.
好吧 伙计们 我们需要准备两份新闻稿
Okay, guys, we need to prep two press releases
为今晚派对上和Mary King的谈话画上句点
for the end of the Mary King talks at the party tonight.
好吧 版本一 Selina Meyer
Okay, version one-- Selina Meyer
结束了财政僵局 拯救了美国
ends fiscal deadlock, saves America.
版本二 Mary King偷走了和睦烟斗 (北美印第安人用来表示和睦)
Version two-- Mary King steals peace pipe,
一分为二 把它弄得一团糟
breaks it in half, shits all over it.
女士 你前夫刚打电话过来
Ma'am, your ex-husband just called.
他说他想去接Catherine
He says that he wants to pick up Catherine.
不 我已经派了车接她 我安排好了
No, I have a car picking her up already. I arranged that.
他就是那样任性又贪婪的蠢货
He is such a conniving, grabby prick.
太典型了 对吧? 难以置信
- Is it typical or what? - Unbelievable.
就是不对 我太讨厌他了
Just wrong. - I hate him so much.
抱歉 我能问原因吗?
Sorry, can I ask why?
这个可以很好的解释
This'll explain it perfectly.
几年前的情人节
Valentine's Day a couple years ago,
他送了我辆黑色的保时捷... 哦
He gave me a black Porsche... - Oh.
用Catherine信任基金的钱买的
that he bought with Catherine's trust fund money.
哦 我是说 他让你体验被捧到天上然后摔下来的感觉
- Oh. - I mean, he just fluffs ya, and then he fucks ya.
哦 好吧 说到...
Yeah. Well, speaking of...
哦 没错 这就是个完美的例子
Oh, yeah, that's a perfect example.
给你 然后
Here you go. So, he took me
那晚他带我去了Cap d'Antibes (法国南部海滨小镇)
to Cap d'Antibes for the night.
哦 他们有了一场疯狂的性交
Yeah, they had crazy intercourse.
可就在那之后他告诉我
Only after which he told me
他卖掉了我们第二套房子
that he sold our second home.
是的 是的 他就像个拿着锤子的肚皮舞者
Yeah, yeah. He's like a belly dancer with a hammer.
那真伤人
That would hurt.
你知道吗?我一点也不担心Andy
You know what? I'm not worried about Andy
因为我要完全忘记他
because I'm gonna completely obliterate him
用我他妈的姿态还有成熟
with my fucking poise and sophistication.
知道我在说什么吗?
You know what I mean?
上帝啊 你听到了吗? 是的 是的
- God, did you hear that? - Yeah, yeah.
她在叫他Andy而不是Andrew
She's calling him Andy instead of Andrew.
已经开始了 什么?
- It's starting. - What?
每次Andy到场
Every time Andy's on the scene,
她就把所有... 轻浮
She gets all... - Giddy.
她就 这种可怕的笑声
She's-- this terrible laugh.
她就这样... 没错 完全正确
- She's like... - Yeah, exactly.
还有... 没错 没错 唔
with a... - Yeah. Yeah. Mm-hmm.
她刚说她恨他 她是
She Just said that She hates him. - She does.
但每次她在他周围的时候...
But every time she gets around him...
就变得奇怪了 就像热铁皮狗上的猫一样 (仿《热铁皮屋顶上的猫》)
It's so weird. It's like a cat on a hot tin dog.
Gary 是的?
- Gary. - Yeah?
你知道我那件红色的? 是的
You know my red thing? - Yeah.
你觉得那件露得够多吗
Do you think that it shows enough skin?
是的 好吧
Yeah. - Okay.
我会是最性感的女人中唯一拥有财政智慧的
I'm gonna be the sexiest woman to ever exude fiscal prudence.
你知道吗?那是个他妈的很难实现的搭配
And you know what? That's a very fucking tough look to pull off.
你不觉得吗 好吧 在那个下面你不能穿内衣
- Don't you think? - Okay, you can't wear a bra with that one.
是的 我知道
Yeah, I know.
Amy 嘿
Amy. - Hey.
嘿 嘿 Ed 你...
- Hey. - Hey, Ed. How are--
所以你已经准备好参加派对了?
So you all ready for the party?
唔 提前打个招呼 我在派对上很疯狂
Um, fair warning, I party pretty hard.
你应该看我跳舞
You should see me dance.
我就无法控制自己 哦
- I can't be controlled. - Oh.
我会做很多顶胯的动作 哦
I Do a lot of pelvic thrusts. - Oh.
非常局部的舞蹈
Just very localized dancing.
很小的轨迹
Very small orbits.
我13岁开始就是派对之星了
I've been wrecking parties since I was 13.
我就像成年礼上的Hunter S. Thompson一样 (美国传奇作家 Gonzo新闻的开创者)
I was like the Hunter S. Thompson of bar mitzvahs.
嘿 副总统在吗?
Hey, is the vice president here?
我不希望我看上去像隐形人
I didn't want it to seem like I was lurking.
是的 是的 不 你不是
Yeah, yeah. No, you're not.
她会很高兴再次见到你
She'll be thrilled to see you again.
副总统女士
Madam Vice President.
唔... 你好?
Uh... hello?
- Hi. - Hi.
唔... Ed
Uh... - Ed.
你知道Ed的 是的
You know Ed. - Yeah.
哦 是的!哦 是的 当然 哦 不
Oh, yes! Oh, yes, of course. Oh, no.
我们 我们 我们 我们 我们在...
We-- we-- we-- we-- we met in...
爱达荷州的犄角旮旯见过 我想是的
in Bumfuck, Idaho, I think it was.
特区 是的 是的
- DC. - Yes, yes.
我开玩笑的时候喜欢那么叫特区
That's what I like to call DC as a joke.
Oh.
好吧 很好 很好
Well... - Great. Great.
希望很快能再次见到您 女士 好的
- I'll see you again soon, ma'am. - Okay.
我们会在那见面 对吧?好的 没错 再见
- We're meeting there, yeah? Okay. - Right. Bye.
嘿 伙计 别为她没有记住你而焦虑 好吗?
Hey, buddy, don't worry that she didn't remember you, okay?
那只是因为你是不存在的人
It's only 'cause you're a nonentity.
他是谁 那是 那是 Ed Webster
- Who is he? - That was-- that's Ed Webster.
他是我今晚的男伴 他经营着你 政治行动委员会波士顿办公室
He's my date for tonight. He runs your PAC's Boston office.
哦 他可有人脉了
- Oh. - He's really connected.
之前是说客 后来做了筹款人
Lobbyist turned fundraiser.
不是在巴士站拿着捐钱桶的 对吧
Not the guy at a bus station with a bucket, right?
好吧 我已经准备好和Andrew较量了
Okay, I am ready to take on Andrew.
我需要我的快乐药丸 一点点快乐
I need my happy pills, a little bit of joy.
那么你觉得怎么样?喜欢吗?
So what do you think? Do you like it?
是的 这 很梦幻 妈妈 对吧
- Yeah, it's-- it's unreal, Mom. - Right?
我是说 你不认为你和你的朋友
I mean, don't you think that you and your friends
可以把这称作一场史诗般的成功吗?
would call this whole thing an epic succeed?
差不多吧 没错
Something like that, yeah.
啊 是你爸爸 正在那做他常干的事
Ah, there's your dad doing that thing that he does.
愉快地和他人交谈?
Pleasantly talking to other people?
你知道他做什么
You know what he does.
他记住每个人的一件小事
He remembers one little thing about each person.
Lawrence 很高兴见到你 你还在跑马拉松么?
Lawrence, nice to see you. You still running marathons?
是的 先生 对的 真令人惊讶你的乳头居然还健在
- Yes, sir. - Right, surprised you still got any nipples left.
还有Jenny 很高兴见到你
And Jenny. Nice to see you.
还记得有次你说
Remember that one time when you said
你很喜欢《暮光之城》 而我认为你在说真正的暮光呢?
you were way into Twilight and I thought you meant the time of day?
不过那确实是一天中交通最危险的时候
It really is the most dangerous time for traffic, though.
请 玩得开心
Please, enjoy yourselves.
Andrew? - Mary.
Andrew? Mary
你好吗? 真高兴见到您 国会女议员
- How are you? - Wonderful to see you, Congresswoman.
妈妈 你邀请了国会多数党领袖来我的生日派对?
Mom, you've invited the House Majority Leader to my birthday party?
是的 甜心 这是一千亿美元的削减
Yeah, sweetheart, it's the 100 billion cutoff.
你听说过了吧? 我当然听说了
- You've heard about that? - Of course I've heard about that.
好吧 所以我们在此时此地 在你的派对上
Okay, so we are fixing the biggest problem facing the world
要处理目前世界面对的最大问题
right here, right now at your party.
那不是挺酷的吗 你不这么认为吗?
So that's kind of cool, don't you think?
你好 哦 你好
- Hello. - Oh, hi.
我给你拿了一杯香槟
I got you a glass of champagne.
谢谢 Rahim 你喝酒?
Thank you, Rahim. You drink alcohol?
是的 女士 哦 你们伊朗人总给人惊喜
- Yes, ma'am. - Oh, you Iranians are full of surprises.
干杯 Salamati
- Cheers. - Salâmati.
他刚刚说了什么? 我不知道
- What did he just say? - I don't know.
胡言乱语吧 我听不懂
Some gibberish. I can't understand him.
嘿 宝贝 等你向所有人问候完
Hey, baby, once you've said hello to everyone,
要不要去泡吧?
do you want to go clubbing?
好 只要不是这里哪里都行
Yeah. Anywhere but here.
Ben 你在这干什么
Ben, what are you doing here?
我和总统谈过 然后呢?
I spoke to POTUS. - Yeah?
他说可以削减失业福利
And he said okay on the cut to unemployment benefits.
其他的协议都完成了
All the other deals are done.
来吧 让我们赶紧弄完然后我们可以开始派对
So come on, let's get this tied up so we can get this party started.
哦 我... 你干了什么?
Yeah, I-- what did you do?
你和另外十个你?
You plus 10'd yourself here?
那是帮你达成协议算账的
Number crunchers to help you finish the deal.
哦 还有一个是指派的司机
Yeah. - And one of them is a designated driver
因为我要一醉方休
because I am going to get fucked up.
你看起来很棒 你就像一件艺术品
You look so good, you're like a work of art.
你让这里所有的东西看起来都像大便
You make this stuff look like shit.
和你相比 那张莫奈的作品...就是坨屎 (印象派开山祖师)
Compared to you, that Monet is a piece of shit.
Selina 你好了吗? 给我五分钟
- Selina, are you ready? - Give me five minutes.
我就去和Andrew说几句 可以吗
I just got to go talk to Andrew, okay?
前夫?三分钟
The ex? Three minutes.
什么 你已经开始谈判了? 我要四分钟
What, are you negotiating already? I'll give you four.
我会让她减到三分钟的 好吗 唔
- I'll cut her off at three, okay? - Mm-hmm.
你好 Selina 你好 Andrew
- Hi, Selina. - Hi, Andrew.
看你问候派对上的所有人真令人开心
It's nice to see you greeting everybody here at the party
就像那是你自己弄的超棒派对一样
as if it was your own fabulous party.
你这是在搞我么? 也许会哦
are You fucking with me? - I Might be.
好吧
All right.
你看起来棒极了 非常感谢
You Look wonderful. - Thank You Very much.
你晒得很黑 怎么弄的?
You're very tanned. What is that?
大开曼岛 我开始玩深水潜水
Grand Cayman. I've been starting to scuba dive.
哦 水下的世界很神奇
Oh. - Magical to be down there.
唔嗯 和那些珊瑚和鱼一起
Uh-huh. - with the coral And the fish.
猥亵那些人鱼 如果不喜欢
Feeling up all the mermaids.
它们就应该包裹得严实点
They should cover up if they don't want it.
如果她们不想要人动手  就不应该做广告
If they don't want action, they shouldn't advertise.
哦 天哪 我们的小Catherine
- Oh, gosh. - Our little Catherine.
她还是那么可爱 唔嗯
- She's still cute. Mm-hmm.
还记得第一间公寓吗?
Remember that first apartment?
是的 我的确记得
Yeah, I do remember that apartment.
那其实是个很不错的公寓
That was a nice apartment, actually.
确实 没错
it was. - Yeah.
你在干什么? 你要求婚吗?
What are you doing? Are you gonna propose?
那你的答案会是什么?
What would your answer be?
我会回答去他娘的耶稣基督啊
My answer would be Jesus fucking Christ.
啊 女士 Mary King很迫切地要和您谈话
Uh, ma'am. Mary King is very anxious to speak with you.
哦 好的 好的 在Catherine的生日上?
- Oh, right. Right. - At Catherine's birthday?
好吧 我正试图避免政府停工
Well, I'm trying to keep the government from shutting down.
哦 你去忙吧 我这就去
- Well, get on it. - I'm getting on it.
没错 好吧
Yeah, okay.
你看到了吗? 他没有逃出我的手掌
Did you see that? I had him in the palm of my hand.
哦 严格地说 女士 他的手抓住了你的手掌
Well, technically, ma'am, he had the palm of your hand in his hand.
哦 你得很小心 宝贝儿
- Oh. - You need to be really careful, sweetie.
Gary 你刚叫我宝贝儿了
Gary, you just called me sweetie.
哦 天哪 我很抱歉
Oh, my God! I'm sorry.
我就是那么叫Dana的 你曾叫过Dana女士吗
- That's what I call Dana. - Did you ever call Dana ma'am?
我干过一次而那很糟糕
I did once and it was awful.
如果我现在喝醉了 你会吻我么
If I were drunk right now, would you kiss me?
是的 不 Gary 我说笑的
- Yeah. - No, Gary, I'm kidding.
对的 没错
Right. - Yeah.
我去拿点喝的
I'm gonna get a drink.
Mary 好吧
- Mary. - Okay!
是时候在这投颗派对炸弹了
It's time to drop a party bomb up in here.
21岁生日快乐 Catherine!
Happy 21st birthday, Catherine!
我想和你谈谈关于计划中的基地关闭事宜
I want to talk to you about targeted base closings.
如果惹毛我选区的选民就不行
Not if it upsets my district.
什么我的老二花活滚床单?
Something sex my dick trick?
你刚说了老二? 老二花活滚床单
did You say dick? - Sex your dick trick.
我不明白你刚刚说的
I don't understand what you just said.
这很可笑 我们得离开这
It was funny. We got to get out of here.
很好 去哪? 不知道 我们会找到地方的
- All right. Where? - I don't know. We'll find someplace.
你知道 在美术馆里你看起来很棒
You know, you look great in an art gallery
因为你就是一件艺术品
'cause you kind of are a work of art.
我是说 我知道我想把你钉在墙上
I mean, I know I'd like to nail you up against a wall.
不 那是善解人意 我那是善解人意
No, that was knowing. I was being knowing.
看起来我们可以做点文章
It looks like we're gonna be able to move
在失业上
on unemployment.
失业福利? 是的
Unemployment benefits? - Yes.
可以动了? 是的
on the table? - Yeah.
好吧 我被授权将职业安全和健康署 的削减数字从25减到17
Okay, I'm authorized to come down on OSHA from 25 to 17.
不 我需要个位数
No, I need a single digit.
我没法给你个位数
I can't give you a single digit.
我们得从别处找东西填补 而你知道你做不到
We'd have to make it up elsewhere and you know you can't do that.
我们会从别处补偿 麻烦等一会
And we are gonna make it up elsewhere. Hang on just a second.
嘿 女孩们 女孩们 麻烦声音小点 可以吗
Hey, gals. Gals, you need to keep it down, okay?
这儿有其他人正试图谈话
There are other people in here trying to have a conversation.
但她拿了我男朋友的号码!
But she took my boyfriend's number!
哦 天哪 是他给我的!
- Oh, my God. - He gave it to me!
你还没有给我失业福利的数字
You haven't given me a number on unemployment benefits.
我的数字会是0.4% 0.4?
- My number's gonna be .4%. - .4?
没错 我不能
- Yeah. - I can't--
我做不来 走吧 不
- I can't do this. Let's go. - No.
我没法在这种噪音下做算数
I can't do math with this kind of noise.
我无法忍受小姑娘了 你没当过小姑娘么?
- I cannot stand teenage girls. - Were you ever one?
从不 我也没有
- Never. - Me neither.
为副总统工作的Amy和Ed
Amy and Ed work for the VP,
亲吻
K-I-S-S-I-N-G.
滚开 Mike 没问题
- Fuck off, Mike. - Sure.
嘿 今晚副总统看起来很性感
Hey, the veep looks smoking tonight.
我好奇要多少杯伏特加下肚
I wonder how much vodka we'd need to have
我们才能一睹罗宾逊夫人风采 (参见电影《毕业生》)
to have a little Mrs. Robinson moment.
这太不尊重了
That is extremely disrespectful.
你在说什么?
What are you talking about?
这是最高赞誉了好么
That's like the highest compliment you can give somebody.
哦 顺便说
Oh, by the way,
我喜欢你们在一起给Dan造成的巨大不爽
I love how much you guys being together is fucking with Dan.
Amy和Dan以前约会过 顺便说
Amy and Dan used to date, FYI.
哦 谢谢这个背景解说 Jonah
Yeah, thanks for the backgrounding, Jonah.
那是不是说你重回市场了?
Does that mean you're back on the market?
抱歉 你这是不是在我约会的时候钓我马子?
I'm sorry, are you hitting on my date during my date?
你有吃药吗?
Are you on meds?
是的 抗生素 保持活力
Yeah, antibiotics. Just keeping fresh.
我精神没有问题
I'm not mentally ill
如果你是在暗示这个的话
if that's what you're implying.
呃 嘿? 大家好
Uh, hello? Hi.
大家好 我就是想
Hi, everyone. I just wanted to say
对我了不起的女儿说几句话
a couple of words to my awesome daughter.
你知道的 我想停下来然后说
You know, I wanted to pause and just say
我认为在这样的时候
that I think at times like these
能和家人和朋友见面真是棒极了
it is great to see family and friends
能倾听家人和朋友
and to hear family and friends.
能诉说和倾听
To be able to talk and to listen
还有讲话和有人聆听
and to speak and to be heard.
我认为有时我们只是需要花些时间
And I think sometimes we need to just take time.
不用太长 我的意思是 大概十分钟或
Not long at all. I mean, maybe 10 minutes or--
哦 或者十五分钟也不错
okay, or maybe 15 is also good.
我建议我们来点有建设性的谈话时间
I'm gonna suggest that we have a little constructive talking time.
那么你们有什么安静些的音乐吗?
So do you have any sort of chillaxing kind of music?
然后你们可以一直播放直到
And then you keep that playing until--
直到...看向我 我给你们信号
only until-- look at me-- I give you a signal.
不是在那之前 没问题
not before. - Sure.
哦 还有生日快乐
Ooh, and happy birthday,
Catherine!
好吧 如果在失业福利上你能给我1%...
- All right. - If you can give me 1% on unemployment benefits...
哦 我可以同意全国卫生研究所减10
- Yeah. - I can go 10 on NIH,
农业补贴上减8
eight off agricultural subsidies.
底线是你去年的预算提案
The baseline is your budget proposal from last year.
对的 好吧 好吧 那些数字加起来?
- Right. Okay. - Okay, those numbers add up?
我加出来是10 12
- I make it 10. - 12.
12?你怎么得到的?
12? How'd you get that?
你忘了能源 当然
- You're forgetting energy. - Of course.
看看这个 那么 我们达成一致了?
Check this out, then. Do we have a deal?
哦 没错 棒极了
Okay, yeah, great.
是的 我们达成一致了 没错!
- Yeah, we have a deal. - Yeah!
这条件真快杀了我了 但我们达成一致了 完成了
- It nearly killed me, but we have a deal. - Put 'er there.
完成了 恭喜
- Put 'er there. - Congratulations.
我无法相信 这不是...
- I can't believe it. - Isn't that--
我无法相信 Mary 这棒极了
I can't believe it, Mary. That's so great.
很好 现在我得说服我的党团了
It's good. Now I have to sell it to my caucus
在我变回南瓜之前 你会成功的
- before I turn into a pumpkin. - You'll do it.
没错 哦 上帝
Yeah. Oh, God.
天哪 21岁的人走得真快
Jesus, 21-year-olds move fast.
是啊 我早知道了
Yeah, tell me about it.
您看起来不错 女士
You look good, ma'am.
哦 谢谢 Jonah 你真的看起来很棒
- Oh, thanks, Jonah. - You look really good.
谢谢 是的 女士
- Thank you. - Yes, ma'am.
你们看过这个了吗
Have you guys seen this?
切蛋糕和宾客们唱生日快乐歌的时候
When the cake was cut and the guests sang 'Happy Birthday, '
副总统无处可寻
the VP was nowhere to be seen.
他们说我和Andrew吵翻了
They're saying I had some sort of huge fight
我们的关系是场骗局
with Andrew and that our relationship is a sham.
这帮禽兽! 先是戴安娜王妃 现在是这个
Monsters. It's like first Princess Diana, now this.
他们认为一开始
They think that at the beginning of the night
你和Andrew是对着镜头做戏
you and Andrew were playing it up to the cameras.
他们再次玩起了说谎者Meyer的烂梗
And they're using this Meyer the Liar bullshit again.
嘿 Mike 谁把那个挖出来的?
Hey, Mike, who dug that up?
不知道 也许是某些记住它的蠢货
I don't know. Probably just some idiot remembered it
然后突然被大肆追捧
and then all of a sudden it got traction.
现在是来自《赫芬顿邮报》
And this is from HuffPo.
Randall Howard即将出版的书宣称
Randall Howard's forthcoming book
您和Andrew在总统选战时的关系
claims your relationship with Andrew during the presidential campaign
是你说的用来迷惑选民的谎言
was a lie invented by you to mislead voters.
那是个谎言 对吧?
That's a lie, right?
没错 那是事实并且确实发生了 但那是Kent撒的谎
- Yeah. - I mean, it's true
and it's what happened, but it's Kent's lie.
不是我 没错
- It's not my lie. - Right.
说谎者Meyer现在可是大热点
Meyer the Liar has huge mo right now.
你知道的 就像人们说的 如果押韵 就会共鸣
You know, as people say, if it rhymes, it chimes.
谁说的?没人那么说
Who says that? No one says that.
我很确定有听人说过
I'm pretty sure I heard someone say that.
哦 现在变成叙述语气了...
Well, it's becoming a narrative right now.
说的是你以前假装了
And the narrative is that you faked it before,
现在肯定也是装出来的
so you must be faking it now.
哦 棒极了 Eeyore驴来了 (小熊维尼里的忧郁驴)
Oh, great. Here's Eeyore.
协议 砰 派对 砰
Deal, boom. Party, boom.
你就是砰砰副总统
You are the boom boom veep.
哦 Catherine很反感昨晚在派对上谈财政的不速之客
Well, Catherine didn't appreciate the fiscal party crashers last night.
今晚Andy和我得带她去吃晚饭
Andy and I have to take her out to dinner tonight
来弥补昨天的派对 所以...
to make up for the party last night, so...
好吧 那会面向公众
Okay, it'll be in public.
所以不管你在做什么 别看起来像在弄虚作假
So whatever you do, don't look like you're faking it
因为说谎者Meyer已经变成了他娘的大雪崩了
because this Meyer the Liar thing is just an avalanche of shit right now.
是的 还用你说 我现在就在雪崩里畅游
Yeah, tell me about it. And I'm swimming in it
还是通过呼吸管呼吸的
and I'm breathing it in through my snorkel.
你得发表一份声明 好吗?
You need to issue a statement, okay?
我的私生活是隐私 是的
my private life is private. - Yes.
还有 Andrew和我 我们相处得还好
Besides, Andrew and I, we get along just fine.
讽刺的是 Ben
Ironically, Ben,
我们事实上相处得是还不错
we actually are getting along just fine.
这很好 装得很像
That's great. That's a great fake.
不 这不是装的 这是真的
No, it's not a fake. That's a real thing.
哦 好吧 棒极了 就那么说
Oh. Well, great. Say that.
我很抱歉
I'm so sorry.
昨晚的派对
That party last night
变成了一个经济峰会
turned into an economic summit.
但是你知道吗? 我们今晚为了你而相聚
But you know what? Here we are now for you.
生日快乐 还有你
- Happy birthday. - And to you,
和鲨鱼同游的男人
a man who swims with sharks.
还开始自由潜水了 真的吗?那是什么?
Also starting free diving. - Really? What is that?
是不是那种尽力憋气憋到底的?
Is that when you try and hold your breath for as long as possible?
就像感恩节晚餐后坐在我妈旁边那样
Kind of like sitting next to my mother after Thanksgiving dinner.
妈妈 你又开始假笑了
Mom, you're doing your fake laugh again.
什么? 嘿 这很好
- What? - Come on, this is nice.
我都看不出来是假笑
I can't tell if it's fake.
你从来都不知道我是不是装的 (三俗双关)
You could never tell if it was fake.
不 我能
Yes, I could.
唔嗯 你是什么 某种专家?
Mm-hmm. What are you, some sort of expert?
在某些领域吧
In certain areas.
现在这是干什么? 这是调情
- What is going on right now? - This is flirting.
你妈妈是个出色的调情者
Your mother is an excellent flirt.
你得做些调情笔记
You should take flirting notes.
这不是调情
This is not flirting.
这就和在facebook上放裸照一样直白
This is like as subtle as putting a nude photo on Facebook.
Selina会注意到这个隐形人吗?
Do you think Selina would notice the invisible man
来自波士顿政治行动委员会办公室的
from the Boston PAC office if I showed up at the office
你觉得如果我穿上政治行动委员会制服的话
in a Pac-Man costume?
我知道 抱歉
I know, I'm sorry.
抱歉 不过你为什么要抱歉?
I'm sorry, why are you sorry?
我不知道
I don't know.
我听到牢骚所以我以为我需要道歉
I heard whining and I assumed I needed to apologize.
你有多长时间没有听我说话了?
How long have you not been listening to me?
我只是很需要密切关注这个
I just really need to watch this because Andrew
因为Andrew就像一座休眠火山
is like a dormant volcano
可能随时爆发
and he can just blow at any second.
我想我要吃些扇贝
I think I'm gonna have the scallops.
我想我要吃 我知道你想要吃什么
- I think I'm gonna have-- - I know what you're gonna have.
你要吃... 别那么做
- You are going to have-- - Don't do that.
唔? 把你的手放下来
Hmm? - Put your hand down.
我没法忍受这种男人至上式的傲慢
I can't stand that alpha male arrogant thing.
我真的没法忍受 Andrew
I really can't stand it, Andrew.
好吧 那不是傲慢
Okay, it's not arrogant.
去你妈的你那么想
And fuck you for thinking so.
原谅我 我只是在预测你的点餐
Forgive me, I was just anticipating your order.
是什么? 羊排
Which was? - Lamb cutlets.
不是
No.
是的 我很抱歉我了解你 Selina
Yeah. I'm sorry I know you, Selina.
原谅我 你对我而言不是个大谜题
Forgive me. You're not a big mystery to me.
而我非常享受这种像打了石膏的僵硬笑容
And I'm very much enjoying the plastered-on smile,
假装一切都很好 因为人们在看着
pretending everything's okay because people are watching.
别这么混蛋 Andrew
Don't be a bastard, Andrew.
你得做出同样的脸
You've got to do the same face.
你也得这么笑 就是这样
You put it on, too. There we go.
好吧 哦 现在这种调情算是比较隐晦了
Okay, well, now this flirting is a little bit more subtle.
那么 Ed Eddie
So, Ed. Eddie.
你认识谁?你知道Ray McCaskill吗?
Who do you know? Do you know Ray McCaskill?
是的 他是很好的人
Yeah, he's a great guy.
我们都很喜欢80年代的友情戏剧
We both are really into '80s buddy comedies,
很讽刺的是这就是我们变成朋友的方式
which is ironically how we became buddies.
炮友吧
Fuck buddies.
Jonah 你为什么在这
Jonah, why are you here?
你真的没有任何事可以做 是吗?
You really don't have anything to do, do you?
瞧 别理他 别理谁?
- Look, ignore him. - Ignore who?
嘿 我觉得这里的那位女士刚刚拍了Selina
Hey, I think that lady right there just took a photo of Selina.
这个?
This one?
我明白你们之间是爱恨交织
I understand that you guys have a love-hate relationship,
但很多人的这些感情都会轮着来
but most people alternate emotions.
他们不会同时展露爱恨两种情绪
They don't experience them at the same time.
我们一直保持着反复无常的关系
We've always had a volatile relationship.
你这么说指的是疯到掉渣吧
By that you mean bat shit crazy.
激情总是当中不可缺少的部分 没错
- Passion was always an integral part. - Yeah.
是的 还有争吵 漫长而辛苦的争吵
Yes, there was fights. Long, hard fights.
之后是漫长而辛苦的...
Followed by long, hard...
和好 对吧?
making up, right?
好吧 我觉得你们马上就要
Okay, I feel like you're actually going to have sex
在这张桌上开干了  而那真的会毁掉我的生日
on this table and that would truly ruin my birthday.
Catherine 算了吧 没人会在桌子上开干的
Catherine, please. Nobody's having sex on the table.
我是说 我们是性爱的动物 当然 哦 天哪
- I mean, we are sexual beings, of course. - Oh, my God.
我们有过性爱 我们 你知道
We had sex. We, you know--
我是说 很棒的性爱 很棒...的性爱
- I mean, great sex. - Great sex.
好吧 我得给我的心理医生发短信了
Well, I'm going to have to text my therapist.
那个不能喝酒是怎么回事?
What's the whole not drinking thing?
我是个贵格教徒 什么?
- I'm a Quaker. - What?
扯淡! 没人是他妈的贵格教徒
Bullshit. No one's a fucking Quaker.
你大概认为保持冷静会让你保持状态
You probably think that staying sober keeps you on top of your game.
哦 猜 我努力工作也努力玩 贱人
Well, guess what. I work hard and I play hard, bitch.
这是我的信条
That's my credo.
我把该死的那个纹在了我的JJ上 还有空余的地方
I got that shit tattooed on my dick with room to spare.
Jonah 你甚至都还不是人
Jonah, you're not even a man.
你只能算是人的草稿
You're like an early draft of a man
那草稿上只随便画了一个巨大的骨架
where they just sketched out a giant mangled skeleton,
可他们没有时间去添加细节
but they didn't have time to add details
比方说上色啦自尊啦之类的东西
like pigment or self-respect.
如果科学怪人是用死人的老二拼起来的话 (参见同名科幻小说及电影)
You're Frankenstein's monster
你就是那个怪物
if his monster was made entirely of dead dicks.
我去洗手间
I'm gonna go to the bathroom.
别在我离开的时候让你们自己难堪
Just try not to embarrass yourselves while I'm gone.
我们会尽量试试
We'll give it a shot.
很高兴见到你
Nice to see you.
唔 抱歉
Um, I'm sorry.
我能打扰一会吗 唔 不行
- Can I interrupt a second? - Uh, no.
看起来这有很多人正在发推特
It just looks like there's a lot of people who are tweeting
还有照相 所以你们大概希望能注意下姿势
and taking pictures, so you might want to be gesture-aware.
还好 谢谢 你可以离开了
It's fine. Thank you. You can go.
好的? 是的 好吧
- Okay? - Yeah, okay.
我想告诉你点事
I want to tell you something.
什么?
What?
唔 公关负责人告诉我
Um, the head of PR
说在上次选举的时候我们公司同时资助了
told me that our company funded super PACs
两边的超级政治行动委员会
on both sides during the last election.
我先被捧上了天
I just was fluffed
然后被狠狠地摔到了地上
and then I got fucked.
我无法相信你刚刚告诉我的事情
I cannot believe what you are telling me.
你知道...微笑
Do you know-- smile.
微笑 你这愚蠢的混蛋 笑开一点
Smile, you stupid asshole. Make it bigger.
就是这样
There you go.
你知道媒体现在是怎么众口一词说我的么?
Do you have any idea how the press is all over me right now?
他们会怎么样报道
And how they are gonna run with the story
我资助我对手的故事?
about me funding my opponent?
你就是个他妈的蠢货
You're a stupid fucking prick.
对吗? 你说
Right? You say it.
我不会那么说
I'm not gonna say that.
好吧 现在发生了什么?
Okay, what happened now?
你们看起来就像要用牛排刀捅对方
You guys look like you're going to stab each other with steak knives.
我们正在吵架 我们也在微笑
We're having a fight and we are smiling
然后摆出虚假的表情 你也能做到 就是这样
and putting a face on and you can do that, too. There you go.
Selina 这只是生意
Selina, this is just business.
我们希望最终能和胜利者一起
We want to end up with the winner at the end.
没有任何私人恩怨在里面 我保证
There's nothing personal about it, I promise.
我甚至不知道这件事
I didn't even know about it.
哦 扯你妈的淡
Oh, that's utter bullshit.
但你知道吗?我会搞定它
But you know what? I'm keeping it together.
我确实会 这些都很好
I really am. It's all good.
我们能保持微笑 保持微笑 没错
We Can Keep smiling. - Keep smiling. Yeah.
我想如果你们继续微笑
I think that if you guys continue to smile,
你们会得永久性的牙关紧闭症
you're actually gonna get permanent lockjaw.
她真有趣
She's so funny.
不是吗? 真讽刺
- Isn't she? - Sarcastic.
我很抱歉打扰你们 我刚接到Kent的电话
I'm sorry to interrupt. I just had a call from Kent.
哦 来恭喜我 因为我促成了昨晚的协议
Oh, to congratulate me 'cause I made the deal last night.
美国感谢你 不客气
- America thanks you. - You're welcome.
总统会暂缓那个协议
POTUS is going to stall on that deal.
不 不 不 他为什么要那么做? 那不对
No, no, no. Why would he want to do that? That can't be right.
哦 在我看来那听起来像是他想政府停工
Well, it sounds to me like he wants a government shutdown
所以他可以责怪国会并让间谍的事情降温
so he can blame it on Congress and take the heat out of the spy story.
你听到了吗 是的
did You hear that? - Yeah.
去他妈的的总统 对吗?  还有去他妈的Kent
Fuck POTUS. Right? And fuck Kent.
他们就是一群混蛋
They're just a bunch of fuckers.
喔 哦 不 不 不
- Uh-oh. - No, no, no.
他们刚刚拍到了?我发火的样子?
Did they just get that? Me being angry?
哦 是的 但我不是对你发火
- Oh, yeah. - But I wasn't being angry with you.
我是说 我之前有对你发火
I mean, I was angry with you before,
但不是现在
but I'm not angry with you now.
我知道那个 亲爱的 首先别叫我亲爱的
- I understand that, honey. - Don't call me honey for starters.
你得冷静下来 你看起来快疯了
You have to calm down. You look crazed.
我们能没收那只电话吗? 我希望我们可以
- Can we confiscate that phone, please? - I wish we could.
我想太迟了 抱歉
- I think it's too late. - Excuse me.
推特上有张照片显示你们在吵架
There's a picture on Twitter and it looks like you guys are fighting.
什么? 就那个? 是的
What? From that? - Yes.
看这个 瞧 这不是事实
Look at this. Look. This is not what it is.
我指向你是因为我被总统弄疯了
I'm pointing to you because I'm mad about POTUS.
我没有说我因为你而对你发火
I wasn't saying that I was angry to you about you.
好吧 你让事情更糟糕了
Okay, Lee, you're just making it worse.
我没有 是他们
I'm not making it worse. They're making it worse.
爸爸 别那么做 你能不能别这么做了?
- Dad, don't do that thing. - Would you just cut that out?
每个人都来唱
Everybody sing.
不 不 不 我们得走了
Nope, nope, nope. We have to go.
好吧 好吧 吹灭你的蜡烛 亲爱的
- Okay. Okay. - Blow out your candles, honey.
有什么意义? 好吧 我来吹
- What's the point? - Okay, I'll do it.
许个愿 那里 灭了
- Make a wish. - There, it's out.
你可以在车里许愿
You can make your wish in the car.
好吧 好吧 把我的东西都拿着
All Right. All Right. - get All my stuff.
哦 不 好吧 我会拿着你的东西
Oh, no, that's fine. I'll get your stuff.
好吧 生日快乐
Okay, happy birthday.
这儿不错
This is good here.
我要出去
I'll get out.
什么?你要在这下车? 是的
What? You're getting out here?
你在说什么? 你不能下去
Yep. - What are You talking about?
我得...等一会
- I've got to go. - Wait a minute.
等等 Andrew 等等 等等 我们得谈谈
Wait. Andrew, wait. Wait. We need to talk.
再见 亲爱的 生日快乐
Bye, honey. Happy birthday.
等等 什么?去他妈的真该死
- Wait, what? - God damn it.
你干什么?逃跑?
What are you doing running away?
我无法相信你 过来这
- I cannot believe you. - Come here.
哦 上帝 你在干什么... 过来这里
- Oh, my God, what are you doing? - Come here right now.
你在干什么? 哦!
What are you doing? Oh!
哦 上帝啊
Oh, my God.
嘿 Catherine
Hey, Catherine.
你拿了个很棒的蛋糕
Pretty nice cake you got there.
你要全部吃掉?
You gonna eat all of it?
你要来一块吗?
Do you want a piece?
我想 你要来块蛋糕吗?
- I do. - You want a piece of the cake?
我滴苍天啊 给你
Jesus fucking Christ. Here.
拿着
Take that.
胡萝卜蛋糕很不错
Carrot cake's good.
你要试试吗? 不要
- You want to try it? - Nope.
都是你的
It's all yours.
我能用手机来切它
I can use my phone to cut it.